<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <DMS_Gun_RailGun.label>Skybolt Retribution</DMS_Gun_RailGun.label>
  <DMS_Gun_RailGun.description>AHWP-88A "Skybolt Retribution" is an 88mm electromagnetic rail-launch system intended as a next-generation ultra-heavy automatroid direct-fire main gun.

A superconducting energy-storage coil and staged acceleration rails launch fin-stabilized sabot rounds at extreme velocity. An autoloader compresses reload time to seconds, while a compact pulse power unit sustains full-power firing. Cryogenic cooling limits rail heating, and recoil-damping hydraulics distribute the impulse across the chassis for stable follow-up shots.</DMS_Gun_RailGun.description>

  <DMS_Bullet_RailGun.label>fin-stabilized rail sabot</DMS_Bullet_RailGun.label>

  <DMS_Gun_LaserGun.label>Verdant Annihilation</DMS_Gun_LaserGun.label>
  <DMS_Gun_LaserGun.description>AHWP-35L "Verdant Annihilation" is a high-energy chemical laser paired with adaptive optics, capable of sweeping a designated area with a devastating beam.

Its variable-wavelength modulation automatically adjusts penetration behavior against different materials—melting armor weak points or detonating critical components with equal ease.</DMS_Gun_LaserGun.description>

  <DMS_Gun_HeavyAutoCannon.label>Metal Storm</DMS_Gun_HeavyAutoCannon.label>
  <DMS_Gun_HeavyAutoCannon.description>A fully automatic suppression weapon built for heavy automatroids.

Seven rotating barrels and assisted feed systems unleash a shredding torrent effective against clustered targets and light vehicles. The modular feed supports quick ammo swaps (AP/HE), while heat-treated barrels and stabilized mounting sustain long bursts.</DMS_Gun_HeavyAutoCannon.description>

  <DMS_Bullet_HeavyAutoCannon.label>30mm autocannon shell</DMS_Bullet_HeavyAutoCannon.label>

  <DMS_Gun_MediumAutoCannon.label>Ripper</DMS_Gun_MediumAutoCannon.label>
  <DMS_Gun_MediumAutoCannon.description>A balanced heavy-weapon platform for heavy automatroids.

Three alternating barrels deliver dense, reliable fire with good mobility. A recoil-compensation system and self-cleaning mechanism reduce jams and maintain stability under harsh conditions.</DMS_Gun_MediumAutoCannon.description>

  <DMS_Bullet_MediumAutoCannon.label>tungsten-core AP round</DMS_Bullet_MediumAutoCannon.label>

  <DMS_Gun_MediumCannon.label>Breacher</DMS_Gun_MediumCannon.label>
  <DMS_Gun_MediumCannon.description>A 57mm rapid-fire cannon designed for modern armor engagements.

Hydraulic buffering and magazine loading combine traditional cannon punch with high rate of fire. Tungsten penetrators defeat armored targets, while programmable airburst rounds devastate exposed infantry.</DMS_Gun_MediumCannon.description>

  <DMS_Bullet_MediumCannon.label>57mm cannon shell</DMS_Bullet_MediumCannon.label>

  <DMS_Weapon_HeavyAutoCannon.label>Rod of Judgment</DMS_Weapon_HeavyAutoCannon.label>
  <DMS_Weapon_HeavyAutoCannon.description>A repurposed 35mm AA cannon firing AHEAD-style airburst fragmentation rounds.

Originally designed for anti-air, it was adapted for ground combat. Fragmentation is represented via explosive effect.</DMS_Weapon_HeavyAutoCannon.description>

  <DMS_Bullet_HeavyAutoCannonBig.label>35mm AHEAD round</DMS_Bullet_HeavyAutoCannonBig.label>

  <DMS_Gun_ChargeAutoCannon.label>Oblivion Calamity</DMS_Gun_ChargeAutoCannon.label>
  <DMS_Gun_ChargeAutoCannon.description>AHWP-30A "Oblivion Calamity" is a 30mm charge-weapon system intended as a next-generation heavy automatroid suppression gun.

Its charge rounds deliver high penetration against armored targets, addressing the lack of anti-armor performance in existing heavy automatroid weapon sets.</DMS_Gun_ChargeAutoCannon.description>

  <DMS_Bullet_ChargeAutoCannon.label>charge round</DMS_Bullet_ChargeAutoCannon.label>

  <DMS_Gun_HeavyCannon.label>Sword of Truth</DMS_Gun_HeavyCannon.label>
  <DMS_Gun_HeavyCannon.description>A 100mm semi-automatic rifled tank gun known for its simple, reliable design.

Widely mounted on armored platforms to engage tanks and heavy armored formations.</DMS_Gun_HeavyCannon.description>

  <DMS_Bullet_HeavyCannon.label>fin-stabilized APFSDS</DMS_Bullet_HeavyCannon.label>
</LanguageData>
